

# CONTACT

+351 910 603 582 anna.collana@gmail.com

LISBON, PORTUGAL







## **TECH SKILLS**

- MERN Stack
- Chart.js
- Redux / Redux Toolkit/ Hooks
- GIT
- REST API
- Module CSS/CSS Components
- Tailwind CSS
- Swagger UI

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Team player
- Communicative
- Reliable and professional
- Organized
- Fast learner
- Determined
- Problem-solver
- Good sense of humour

## LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Portuguese Fluent
- Russian Native
- Ukrainian Native
- Korean Elementary

# ANASTASIIA LOZOVYCH

## JUNIOR MERN FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am an enthusiastic, goal-oriented professional with more than 10 years of experience in Hospitality and Customer Support fields located in Portugal, Brazil, Australia, USA and Ukraine. Currently, looking to start a new career as Junior MERN Full Stack Developer. Great team work ability, detail orientated, effective communication and politeness, excellent efficiency and responsibility. Fluent in English, Russian, Ukrainian, Portuguese languages, studying Korean at the moment.

#### **PROJECTS**

• MERN Social Media App (in progress of Frontend, Backend is done)

The App enables the User to use it as a social media platform to interact with people and friends, upload and delete photos, comments and likes.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS Module, React.js, Redux, Redux hooks, Redux-toolkit, responsive design, Node.js, Multer, Express.js

#### WEATHER

This App shows weather forecast for a day as well as for the next 7 days based on your current location. You are able to search weather in another cities and add them to your favourite list. Simply by clicking on cities in the list you can see the forecast without searching them again. Ready to use in all devices.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS Module, React.js, Redux, Redux hooks, Redux-toolkit, Redux-Thunk, responsive design

## • MOVIE FINDER

This website is able to find the right movie for you in simple and fast manner. Very easy in use, full of details about movies, cast and reviews.

Tech Stack: HTML, Styled Components CSS, React.js, React Router, responsive design

#### SLIM MOM

This is an App that helps young women lose weight by controlling daily calorie intake and showing unrecommended list of products based on personal information.

Tech Stack: HTML, Styled Components, React.js, React Router, Redux, Redux Persist, responsive design

## • NodeJS Backend for Kapusta Project

I worked in collaboration with my teammate on developing Backend Node.js for the Kapusta App

Tech Stack: Node.js, Express.js, Multer, Cors, Joi, Mongoose, MongoDB, Morgan, Swagger

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

• CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE 2022-2023

Excellent team work experience in fast paced under pressure environment, ability in finding the best solution, highly professional conversation manners. Worked in Portuguese company Teleperformance, supporting Russian and English speaking customers.

• RESTAURANT MANAGER 2013 - 2021

I have great deal of experience working as Restaurant Manager starting just from Assistant Waitress, getting promotion to Manager in 5 different countries: USA, Ukraine, Brazil, Australia and Portugal.

## **EDUCATION**

GOIT SCHOOL

IT School GOIT (Ukraine) | jan 2021 - aug 2021 MERN Full-Stack Developer

• ODESSA INTERNATIONAL HUMANITARIAN UNIVERSITY

Bachelor Degree in Translation and Linguistics | sep 2008 - july 2012